# 哈喽 大家好
Hello, everybody.
# 今天我们来聊一下最近更新的这个状态
Today we're going to talk about the recently updated status
# 在发布这个大盘鸡之前
Before posting the Big Plate Chicken
# 我就已经预感到会有粉丝说我们这个
I already had a feeling there would be fans saying that
# 白案的手法不熟练 不正宗
the dough kneading techniques are not proficient enough
# 其实我也确实承认我这个不是我的强项
Actually, I do admit dough kneading is not my strong strength.
# 但是我也正在努力学习当中
But I have been studying hard on it.
# 其实这个面皮子的比例我用（尝试）了很多次
In fact, I've tried that dough ratio many times.
# 而且用不同的时间 不同的水
And at different kneading times, with different amounts of water.
# 不同的盐做了很多实验
A lot of experiments with different amounts of salt.
# 在这之前呢网上有很多类似的教学
Before that, there were many similar tutorials on the Internet.
# 但是这个比例都是五花八门吧
But there are so many different dough receipts.
# 有一斤这个高筋面粉加220克的水啊
Some receipts say a kilo of strong white flour with 220g of water,
# 五克的盐啊
and 5g of salt...
# 就是说什么比例都有
There are a lot of different flour to water ratios.
# 其实这也不算太严谨
Actually, they are all not very precise.
# 水太少的话和这个面太干啦
If the water amount is too little, the dough will be too dry
# 一拉就断而且发不出来
It will break when I pull it.
# 我在这个面粉500克的基础上面
I use 500 grams of flour as basis,
# 五克清水往上面加一直加到300克为最适合
add 5 grams of water each time until it reaches 300 grams,
# 加到320克为上限
Maximum of 320 grams.
# 如果你再继续在320克上面加水
If you continue to add water exceeding 320 grams,
# 那这个就彻底的稀了
then the dough will be too watery.
# 就是说300克是一个最适合的一个比例
This means 300 grams is the perfect ratio.
# 然后盐的话在八克到十克
The amount of salt is about 8 to 10 grams,
# 根据每个地方盐的咸度来决定
depending on the saltiness of each salt.
# 面粉呢最好选择高筋面粉
The best choice of flour is strong white flour with high gluten.
# 因为这个高筋面粉当中它的蛋白质更高
Because it contains more protein.
# 所以它就更加的劲道
That's why it's more powerful.
# 中筋面粉和低筋面粉的话
If using medium or low gluten plain flour,
# 它的蛋白质少
It has less protein.
# 然后的话它弹性就没那么好
Then the dough will not be so flexible.
# 因此我们在拍摄的这个时候
So at this time during the this video shooting,
# 这个面皮子我们已经
I've made the dough
# 已经做了最少一二十遍了
for at least a dozen times.
# 然后把这个烹饪的数据啊已经记录下来了
And I've recorded the data of each kneading.
# 在没有这些经验和数据的支撑情况下
Without such experience and data support,
# 我们也不会贸然去拍
We would not shoot this video.
# 因为教学的意义嘛
Because that's what teaching is all about.
# 它不是来误导大家
It's not here to mislead people.
# 是跟大家分享一个正确的比例
It's about sharing a correct ratio with you.
# 比如说之前拍的传统富顺豆花
For example, in the previous video of the traditional "Fushun Douhua",
# 我们就耗费了大概100斤黄豆 当然是泡胀了
We experimented about 100 jin (50 grams) of soybeans, which, of course, was soaked up.
# 当然失败的食材
Of course the food waste
# 还是由我们家里面这些鸡鸭那些消耗掉了
was consumed by the chickens and ducks in our house.
# 以及现在拍的大盘鸡和面皮子为例
For the video of large plate of chicken and flat noodles,
# 也试验了一二十次
I've tried the receipt a dozen times.
# 这也就是为什么我们更新的频率比较低的原因
That's why now we update our content less frequently.
# 豆花儿制作的过程这个周期已经超过了十天
We spent more than ten days to make the "Douhua" video.
# 我们从来没有过这么长时间拍一个视频
We've never shot a video in such a long time before.
# 然后以前的技术总结里面有文字
Additionally, the previous technical summary only had text in it.
# 但是没有失败的对比
But no visually comparisons of the successful and failure dishes.
# 而现在有 因为我们是真的在失败
And now there is, because we are really failing.
# 所以我们要把它记录下来
So we have to document it.
# 我这个失败
Document every failure.
# 然后让这个大家来避开烹饪当中的一个坑
I am aimed to help you to avoid one of the pitfalls of cooking.
# 虽然我们没有办法像以前一样保持高频率的更新
While we could not maintain as high a frequency of video updates as before
# 但是我一直都在用心追求这个视频的质量
But I've always been dedicated to the quality of each video.
# 就是观感体验嘛
I want you have a better visual experience when watching my videos.
# 还有这个数据经验的支撑
And I want cooking data to back up my teaching.
# 就是烹饪的时候趟过了哪些坑
To show you the pitfalls of cooking.
# 记录了一些失败的数据和成功的数据
Some data on failures and successes were recorded
# 最后感谢大家能够一如既往的支持我们
Finally, thank you all for being able to support us as always!
# 和理解包容我们
And embrace us with your kind understandings.
# 本期视频就聊到这里拜拜
That's all for this video. Bye.